kagi.com 2015-12-23

# Kagi Marketplace: Index

### What is the Kagi Privacy Policy?

This privacy policy describes the information Kagi collects and what is done with it. Should you have any further privacy questions not covered by this policy, please email [help@kagi.com](mailto:help@kagi.com), please put "Privacy Policy Question" in the subject line. 

Please note that this privacy policy applies to Kagi only. This privacy policy does not cover information collected by non-Kagi web sites accessible from the Kagi web site, nor by any third parties associated with Kagi, including the product suppliers.

### The Information Kagi Collects

Kagi primarily collects, uses and stores your information when you visit a Kagi web site, purchase products from Kagi or when you communicate with Kagi (email, web, phone, fax, postal letter, etc.). Every order form asks for personally identifiable information such as your name, contact information, and payment information. In addition, our order forms can be customized by each of our participating product suppliers, so you may be asked to provide additional information other than that which Kagi normally collects. 

When you interact with Kagi, information on how you communicated with Kagi is collected. The information is primarily used to understand you as a potential customer and so that Kagi may have alternate ways of communicating with you should the information you provide be inadequate. Information on how you communicated with Kagi may include: the Internet address of the computer you used, the language you selected when viewing the order form, the browser type, the security level used to view a web page, the currency in which you viewed prices, the return email address shown in your email messages, the return address on postal envelopes, the return fax number on faxes, the phone number used when calling, and any other information that may be gathered from your communication.

Also, when you allow it, Kagi uses web browser "Cookies." Cookies generally allow Kagi to identify you as someone who has previously visited the Kagi web site. The use of Cookies is now common practice for most commercial web sites, such as Kagi. 

### How Kagi uses the information

The information is primarily used to: determine whether to accept your purchase information; enable our product suppliers to deliver goods, services or information; provide notices regarding goods or services that you may purchase; and improve our business.

### Information sharing

Access to financial payment information such as credit card, debit card information or, bank account information is restricted to Kagi employees and external service providers on a need to know basis. Product suppliers are never provided the financial account number nor the expiration date nor the card identification value (CID or CVV2) for credit or debit cards. Product suppliers may be given the payment type (Visa, Mastercard, Cash, Check,...), account holder name and address, and any responses provided by your financial institution concerning the validity of the information you have provided to Kagi. From time to time Kagi may use external service providers who need to know all your financial payment information to help verify the information provided or to help Kagi make business decisions. Each person or entity that needs to know all your financial payment information has a contractual obligation, with Kagi, to maintain the privacy of that financial payment information.

To ensure that you receive your purchased product(s), all other information collected by Kagi and any additional communications that might be related to your purchase, may be passed to the appropriate product suppliers. Additionally, all other information may be shared with external service providers to help verify the information provided or to help Kagi make business decisions. Such third party partners and product suppliers may use the information to maintain various databases related to your purchase, fulfill purchases, provide technical support, or provide you with information about Kagi, the product, or the product supplier.

Kagi may transfer the information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Kagi participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Kagi's assets.

Kagi aggregates statistics about the information that is collected and may share the aggregated statistics with third parties in order to improve and market our services. Aggregated statistics do not uniquely identify you.

Kagi will disclose all information of any type if Kagi believes that Kagi is required to do so by law, regulation or other government authority, or to prevent harm to yourself or others.

### Information protection

Kagi employs both procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service, to protect your information. Such measures are, within reason, designed to protect all the information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction.

### Information updates

You may contact Kagi at [help@kagi.com](mailto:help@kagi.com) to update any of your information.

### Kagi privacy policy changes

Kagi reserves the right to change this privacy policy, at will, without notice, and will post any revisions at [http://shop.kagi.com](http://shop.kagi.com/) on the Kagi web site. Kagi encourages you to review this privacy policy on a regular basis for any changes. Your use of the Kagi web site will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

This privacy policy, dated 31 Aug 2011, replaces the previous policy, dated 12 Oct 2010. Certain links and grammatical errors were corrected.
